http://www.kidsafewa.com.au/privacy

MenuAbout us CloseOur BoardOur PartnersPublicationsKidsafe WA’s New HomeHome Safety CloseWorkshopsSafety Demonstration HouseOnline Safety Demonstration HouseChild Safety AppVideosResourcesPlay Safety CloseWorkshopsPlay @ Kidsafe WASports Safety AppVideosResourcesRoad Safety CloseWorkshopsChild Car Restraint GuidelinesChild Car Restraint Fitting, Checking & Advice ServiceChild Car Restraint Hiring ServiceHot Cars CampaignVideosResourcesProfessionals CloseSchoolsAccredited TrainingProfessional DevelopmentWA Consumer Product Advocacy NetworkWA Childhood Injury Bulletins & ReportsOther ResearchFacilitator’s GuidesResourcesResourcesEvents CloseWorkshopsRegional Visits
Privacy
Privacy Policy
Kidsafe WA recognises that your privacy is very
important to you and that you have a right to control your personal
information. We know
that you care how information about you is used and
shared and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and
sensibly.
This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting
our web site you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy
Notice.
What personal information do we gather?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalise and continually improve your shopping experience with us.
We record the following information
Information You Give Us: We
receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us
in any other way.
You can choose not to provide certain
information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of
our features. We
use the information that you provide for such
purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for
you, improving
our site, and communicating with you.Other information: We receive
and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us.
For example, like
many Web sites, we use “cookies,” to track your
purchases and when you are logged onto our site. If you have cookies
switched off
you will not be able to purchase from this site
or log in for special members’ pricing or offers.E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we may receive a confirmation when you
open e-mail from us if your computer supports such capabilities.
What about cookies?
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer
to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser to enable our
systems to recognize
your browser and to provide features such as storage
of items in your shopping cart and logging in or out of the website.
The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers
will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies,
how to have the
browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or
how to disable cookies altogether. However cookies allow you to take
full advantage
of some of our features, and we thus recommend that
you leave them turned on.
Do we share the information we receive?
We will not collect any personal information about
you except when you knowingly provide it. We know that providing
personal information
is an act of trust and we take this seriously. Under
no circumstances will your personal information be used for any other
purpose
than intended. We will not supply or sell these
details to any third party whatsoever with the following exceptions.
Business Transfers: As we
continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses and
assets. In such transactions,
customer information generally is one of the
transferred business assets. Also, in the event that we sell our
business, customer
information will of course be one of the
transferred assets.Protection of our business and others:
We may release account and other personal information when we believe
release
is appropriate to comply with law or to protect
the rights, property, or safety of our business, our users, or others.
This includes
exchanging information with other companies and
organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction, and
supplying of
information to Law Enforcement agencies.
How secure is information about me?
We work to protect the security of your information
during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which
encrypts sensitive
financial information you input during the ordering
process.
Children
We generally do not sell products for purchase by
children, as we require credit card details, cheque or money order, or
an account. If
you are under 18, you may use our site but we
reserve the right not to accept your order if we believe that to sell to
you is against
the law, you do not have legitimate authority to
authorise a purchase, you do not have the means to purchase or pay, that
our products
may be used inappropriately, or our products could
cause harm.
What choices do I have?
You can always choose not to provide information by
not completing web forms and turning your cookies off. However, you will
not be able
to purchase on this site while cookies are switched
off.
For more information about our privacy policy please contact us.
MAKE A KIDSAFE WA DONATION
DONATE
Copyright 2020 KidsafeWA. All Rights Reserved.
Shopping Terms | Privacy | Disclaimer | Contact Us | Powered by Kodama Digital
[ Placeholder content for popup link ]
WordPress Download Manager - Best Download Management Plugin
Close
